{
    "questions": [
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "What is the rarest M&M color?",
            "correct_answer": "Brown",
            "answer_options": [
                "Blue",
                "Red",
                "Green",
                "Brown"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "In what year were the first Air Jordan sneakers released?",
            "correct_answer": "1984",
            "answer_options": [
                "1999",
                "2012",
                "1976",
                "1984"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "In a bingo game, which number is represented by the phrase “two little ducks”?",
            "correct_answer": "22",
            "answer_options": [
                "77",
                "44",
                "11",
                "22"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "Tennis star Serena Williams won which major tournament while pregnant with her first child?",
            "correct_answer": "The Australian Open",
            "answer_options": [
                "French Open",
                "Wimbledon",
                "US Open",
                "The Australian Open"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "Which singer’s real name is Stefani Joanne Angelina Germanotta?",
            "correct_answer": "Lady Gaga",
            "answer_options": [
                "Whitney Houston",
                "Mariah Carey",
                "Christina Aguilera",
                "Lady Gaga"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "Where were the Declaration of Independence, the Constitution, and the Bill of Rights stored during World War II?",
            "correct_answer": "Fort Knox",
            "answer_options": [
                "The White House",
                "10 Downing Street",
                "The kremlin",
                "Fort Knox"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "What's the biggest animal in the world?",
            "correct_answer": "Blue Whale",
            "answer_options": [
                "Elephant",
                "Giraffe",
                "Lion",
                "Blue Whale"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "hard",
            "question": "How many times has andy Murray won wimbledon playing singles?",
            "correct_answer": "Twice",
            "answer_options": [
                "Once",
                "Four Times",
                "Twenty Times",
                "Twice"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "Which country is brie cheese originally from?",
            "correct_answer": "France",
            "answer_options": [
                "Germany",
                "Netherlands",
                "Poland",
                "France"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "What is the name of the capital of Iceland?",
            "correct_answer": "Reykjavík",
            "answer_options": [
                "Klausturholar",
                "Skutustadhir",
                "Dave",
                "Reykjavík"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "What year did Margret Thatcher die?",
            "correct_answer": "2013",
            "answer_options": [
                "1997",
                "2003",
                "2006",
                "2013"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "What painted the Mona Lisa?",
            "correct_answer": "Leonardo da Vinci",
            "answer_options": [
                "Vincent van Gog",
                "Rembrandt",
                "Raphael",
                "Leonardo da Vinci"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "What planet is the closest to the sun?",
            "correct_answer": "Mercury",
            "answer_options": [
                "Pluto",
                "Venus",
                "Saturn",
                "Mercury"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "Who plays Delboy Trotter in Only Fools and Horses?",
            "correct_answer": "David Jason",
            "answer_options": [
                "Kenneth MacDonald",
                "Roy Heather",
                "Nicholas Lyndhurst",
                "David Jason"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "Which country is the largest in the world?",
            "correct_answer": "Russia",
            "answer_options": [
                "United States Of America",
                "Australia",
                "Africa",
                "Russia"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "hard",
            "question": "Which city had the first ever fashion week?",
            "correct_answer": "New York City",
            "answer_options": [
                "London",
                "Paris",
                "Los Angeles",
                "New York City"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "What nut is in the middle of a Ferrero Rocher?",
            "correct_answer": "Hazelnut",
            "answer_options": [
                "Peanut",
                "Almonds",
                "Cashew",
                "Hazelnut"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "computer science",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "What goes GPU stand for?",
            "correct_answer": "Graphic Processing Unit",
            "answer_options": [
                "Graphic Prototype Unit",
                "Garbage Processing Unit",
                "Gaming Processing Unit",
                "Graphic Processing Unit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "computer science",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "What does CSS stand for?",
            "correct_answer": "Cascading Style Sheets",
            "answer_options": [
                "Cascading Sketch Sheet",
                "Copy Style Sheet",
                "Case Study Sheets",
                "Cascading Style Sheets"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "computer science",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "In programming what name is given to the data type which represents decimal numbers?",
            "correct_answer": "Floating Point Numbers",
            "answer_options": [
                "Integers",
                "Strings",
                "Number",
                "Floating Point Numbers"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "computer science",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "What is a variable?",
            "correct_answer": "A variable is a location in memory that we use to store data",
            "answer_options": [
                "A variable is a number",
                "A variable is a message input by the user",
                "A variable is a floating point number",
                "A variable is a location in memory that we use to store data"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "computer science",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "What do you call a portable computer?",
            "correct_answer": "Laptop",
            "answer_options": [
                "RAM",
                "CPU",
                "Macbook",
                "Laptop"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "computer science",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "What storage size is the largest?",
            "correct_answer": "1TB",
            "answer_options": [
                "1GB",
                "10GB",
                "55000Bytes",
                "1TB"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "computer science",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "What is the most used search engine?",
            "correct_answer": "Google",
            "answer_options": [
                "Yahoo",
                "Bing",
                "SOSO",
                "Google"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "computer science",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "What do you use to click stuff?",
            "correct_answer": "Mouse",
            "answer_options": [
                "Keyboard",
                "Headphones",
                "RAM",
                "Mouse"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "computer science",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "Which line do you use to connect to the internet?",
            "correct_answer": "Ethernet",
            "answer_options": [
                "Phone Line",
                "USB",
                "SSD",
                "Ethernet"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "computer science",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "In what decade was the Internet first implemented?",
            "correct_answer": "1960s",
            "answer_options": [
                "1950s",
                "1940s",
                "1980s",
                "1960s"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "computer science",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "What do you call a computers core component?",
            "correct_answer": "Motherboard",
            "answer_options": [
                "CPU",
                "GPU",
                "Chipset",
                "Motherboard"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "computer science",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "ISP stands for?",
            "correct_answer": "Internet Service Provider",
            "answer_options": [
                "Internet Security Protocols",
                "Internet Survey Period",
                "Integrated Service Provider",
                "Internet Service Provider"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "computer science",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "Google Chrome is an?",
            "correct_answer": "Web Browser",
            "answer_options": [
                "Any person browsing the web",
                "News Reader",
                "Web Scraping Service",
                "Web Browser"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "computer science",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "The 'http' you type at the beginning of any site's address stands for?",
            "correct_answer": "Hyper Text Transfer Protocol",
            "answer_options": [
                "HTML Transfer Technology Process",
                "Hyperspace Terms and Tech Protocol",
                "Hyperspace Techniques & Tech Progress",
                "Hyper Text Transfer Protocol"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "computer science",
            "difficultly": "hard",
            "question": "Lately you hear a clatter from your computer, especially when you load a program or call up information. What's going on?",
            "correct_answer": "Your hard disk may be headed for failure",
            "answer_options": [
                "It's infested with reindeer",
                "A loud metallic clatter is normal",
                "A loose wire is hitting the cooling fan",
                "Your hard disk may be headed for failure"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "computer science",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "In a website browser address bar, what does “www” stand for?",
            "correct_answer": "World Wide Web",
            "answer_options": [
                "World Wide Website",
                "World Web Word",
                "Web Wide World",
                "World Wide Web"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "music",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "Which English Sir has had No. l’s in the 50’s, 60’s, 70’s, 80’s and 90’s?",
            "correct_answer": "Cliff Richard",
            "answer_options": [
                "Freddie Mercury",
                "David Bowie",
                "Ali Campbell",
                "Cliff Richard"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "music",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "What is the name of the duet recorded by Robbie Williams and Gary Barlow in 2010?",
            "correct_answer": "Shame",
            "answer_options": [
                "No Regrets",
                "Rule The World",
                "Back for Good",
                "Shame"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "music",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "What was the name of the Scottish musican who shot to fame in 2021 with a version of the sea shanty Wellerman?",
            "correct_answer": "Nathan Evans",
            "answer_options": [
                "Care Rose",
                "Lewis Capaldi",
                "Ed Sheeran",
                "Nathan Evans"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "music",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "Which Canadian recording artist twice appeared in the Top 10 of the UK Singles Charts in April 2021 with 'Peaches' and 'Hold On'?",
            "correct_answer": "Justin Bieber",
            "answer_options": [
                "Drake",
                "Michael Buble",
                "Celine Dion",
                "Justin Bieber"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "music",
            "difficultly": "hard",
            "question": "Complete the name of the Dojo Cat track which briefly topped the UK Singles Chart in April 2021; 'Kiss Me ...?'",
            "correct_answer": "More",
            "answer_options": [
                "Again",
                "Twice",
                "Loads",
                "More"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "music",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "Which well-known musican opened 2021 with the first UK Number 1 of the year?",
            "correct_answer": "Ed Sheeran",
            "answer_options": [
                "Robbie Williams",
                "Lewis Capaldi",
                "KSI",
                "Ed Sheeran"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "music",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "Which track by Olivia Rodrigo taken from the album 'Sour' topped the UK Singles Chart for five weeks in June 2021?",
            "correct_answer": "Good 4 U",
            "answer_options": [
                "Drivers License",
                "Deja vu",
                "Hope ur ok",
                "Good 4 U"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "music",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "Which Harry Styles track which won best 'British Single' at the Brit Awards 2021 opens with the lyric 'Tastes like strawberries on a summer evenin''?",
            "correct_answer": "Watermelon Sugar",
            "answer_options": [
                "Kiss You",
                "Adore You",
                "Falling",
                "Watermelon Sugar"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "When did world war two start ?",
            "correct_answer": "1939",
            "answer_options": [
                "1957",
                "1919",
                "1958",
                "1939"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "What is the largest animal in the world?",
            "correct_answer": "Blue Whale",
            "answer_options": [
                "Lion",
                "Giraffe ",
                "Crocodile",
                "Blue Whale"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "What did the romans call Scotland?",
            "correct_answer": "Caledonia",
            "answer_options": [
                "The Scotsland",
                "Highlands",
                "Bitter Cold Land",
                "Caledonia"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "Who was Henry VIIIs last wife?",
            "correct_answer": "Catherine Parr",
            "answer_options": [
                "Catherine Howard",
                "Jane Seymour",
                "Catherine Of Aragon",
                "Catherine Parr"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "What are the five colours of the Olympic rings?",
            "correct_answer": "Blue, Yellow, Black, Green and Red",
            "answer_options": [
                "Blue, Orange, Black, Green and Red",
                "Blue, Yellow, Pink, Green and Red",
                "Blue, Yellow, Black, Lime and red",
                "Blue, Yellow, Black, Green and Red"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "What is the most famous Mexican beer?",
            "correct_answer": "Corona",
            "answer_options": [
                "Victoria Mexican Lager",
                "Pacifico",
                "Tecate",
                "Corona"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "Which US motorbike company is known by the initials 'HD'?",
            "correct_answer": "Harley Davidson",
            "answer_options": [
                "Arch Motorcycle",
                "Indian Motorcycle",
                "Crocker Motorcycle Company",
                "Harley Davidson"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "Which South African city is known as 'Mother City'?",
            "correct_answer": "Cape Town",
            "answer_options": [
                "Johannesburg",
                "Pretoria",
                "Durban",
                "Cape Town"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "Which author created the book character Hermione Granger",
            "correct_answer": "JK Rowling",
            "answer_options": [
                "William Shakespeare\t",
                "Danielle Steel",
                "Jackie Collins",
                "JK Rowling"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "The Spanish resort Benidorm sits on which sea?",
            "correct_answer": "Mediterranean Sea",
            "answer_options": [
                "Caribbean Sea",
                "Gulf of Mexico",
                "North Pacific Ocean",
                "Mediterranean Sea"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "Koreatown is a well known area of which US west coast city?",
            "correct_answer": "Los Angeles",
            "answer_options": [
                "San Francisco ",
                "New York City",
                "Las Vegas ",
                "Los Angeles"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "What is the official language of the Canadian city Quebec?",
            "correct_answer": "French",
            "answer_options": [
                "English",
                "Spanish",
                "Russian",
                "French"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "computer science",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "Which European country uses the '.es' internet address?",
            "correct_answer": "Spain",
            "answer_options": [
                "United Kingdom",
                "France",
                "Poland",
                "Spain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "The 1964 and 2020 Olympic Summer Games were held in which Japanese city?",
            "correct_answer": "Tokyo",
            "answer_options": [
                "Koyto",
                "Hiroshima",
                "Yokohama",
                "Tokyo"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "Which US city is known for being the home of the US automobile industry?",
            "correct_answer": "Detroit",
            "answer_options": [
                "New York City",
                "Chicago",
                "Boston",
                "Detroit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "Which city beginning with 'L' is the third largest city in France?",
            "correct_answer": "Lyon",
            "answer_options": [
                "Lille",
                "Le Havre",
                "Le Mans",
                "Lyon"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "The Olo'upena Falls are in which country of the Americas?",
            "correct_answer": "United States (Hawaii)",
            "answer_options": [
                "Canada",
                "Brazil",
                "Cuba",
                "United States (Hawaii)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": " Which city in what is now the United States, can trace its origins back to 1626 when it was a trading post known as New Amsterdam?",
            "correct_answer": "New York",
            "answer_options": [
                "Boston",
                "Philadelphia",
                "Seattle",
                "New York"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "The Royal Albert Dock is found in which UK city?",
            "correct_answer": "Liverpool",
            "answer_options": [
                "Edinburgh",
                "Manchester",
                "London",
                "Liverpool"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "music",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "Shane, Brian, Mark, Kian and Nicky made up which Irish boyband?",
            "correct_answer": "Westlife",
            "answer_options": [
                "One Direction",
                "Take That",
                "The Beatles",
                "Westlife"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "In 2018, twelve boys and their football coach were rescued after two weeks in a flooded cave situated in which country?",
            "correct_answer": "Thailand",
            "answer_options": [
                "China",
                "Philippines ",
                "Tawian",
                "Thailand"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "Which swimming stroke is named after an insect?",
            "correct_answer": "Butterfly",
            "answer_options": [
                "Dragonfly",
                "Beatle",
                "Ant",
                "Butterfly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "What is a female deer called?",
            "correct_answer": "Doe",
            "answer_options": [
                "Queen",
                "Sow",
                "Cow",
                "Doe"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "What is the only bird that can hover in the air and also ﬂy backwards?",
            "correct_answer": "Hummingbird",
            "answer_options": [
                "Golden eagle",
                "Barn owl",
                "House sparrow",
                "Hummingbird"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "Which is the third largest of the Channel Islands?",
            "correct_answer": "Alderney",
            "answer_options": [
                "Sark ",
                "Guernsey",
                "Jersey",
                "Alderney"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "What do the numbers add up to on the opposite sides of a dice?",
            "correct_answer": "Seven",
            "answer_options": [
                "Six",
                "Ten",
                "Eight",
                "Seven"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "In the zodiac, which animal is linked with Capricorn?",
            "correct_answer": "Goat",
            "answer_options": [
                "Lion",
                "Dog",
                "Bear",
                "Goat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "How long is there between rounds in boxing?",
            "correct_answer": "One minute",
            "answer_options": [
                "Eight minutes",
                "Three minutes",
                "Five minutes",
                "One minute"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "Who was known as the lady with the lamp?",
            "correct_answer": "Florence Nightingale",
            "answer_options": [
                "Margaret McCoubrey",
                "Winifred Carney",
                "Dr Elizabeth Bell",
                "Florence Nightingale"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "In an English trial, how many people sit on the jury?",
            "correct_answer": "12",
            "answer_options": [
                "20",
                "4",
                "10",
                "12"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "Marcel Desailly was a World Cup winner playing for which country?",
            "correct_answer": "France",
            "answer_options": [
                "Belgium",
                "Poland",
                "Germany",
                "France"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "On a standard European roulette wheel which number appears on the green?",
            "correct_answer": "Zero",
            "answer_options": [
                "Three",
                "Five",
                "Two",
                "Zero"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "What number is,,dos” in Spanish?",
            "correct_answer": "Two",
            "answer_options": [
                "One",
                "Three",
                "Four",
                "Two"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "In.which game do you draw part of a gallows for every wrong answer?",
            "correct_answer": "Hangman",
            "answer_options": [
                "Word Search",
                "Who said what?",
                "Scramble",
                "Hangman"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "hard",
            "question": "Brights’ disease affects which organs of the body?",
            "correct_answer": "Kidneys",
            "answer_options": [
                "Heart",
                "Liver",
                "Lungs",
                "Kidneys"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "How many kings of England have been called Philip?",
            "correct_answer": "None",
            "answer_options": [
                "Ten",
                "Two",
                "Five",
                "None"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "How many stomachs does a cow have?",
            "correct_answer": "Four",
            "answer_options": [
                "None",
                "Two",
                "One",
                "Four"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "Which city in the world has the largest population?",
            "correct_answer": "Shanghai",
            "answer_options": [
                "Tokyo",
                "Seoul",
                "Chongqing",
                "Shanghai"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "Whose ship was the first to sail around the world?",
            "correct_answer": "Ferdinand Magellan",
            "answer_options": [
                "James Cook",
                "Francis Drake",
                "Ben Ainslie",
                "Ferdinand Magellan"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "music",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "“Freedom” was the first UK top ten hit for which member of take that?",
            "correct_answer": "Robbie Williams",
            "answer_options": [
                "Gary Barlow",
                "Howard Donald",
                "Mark Owen",
                "Robbie Williams"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "Moving anti-clockwise on a dartboard what is the number next to 4?",
            "correct_answer": "18",
            "answer_options": [
                "19",
                "20",
                "14",
                "18"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "Who pricked her finger on a spinning wheel and slept for 100 years?",
            "correct_answer": "Princess Aurora",
            "answer_options": [
                "Belle",
                "Snow White",
                "Cinderella",
                "Princess Aurora"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "In which team game do you try to move backwards all the time?",
            "correct_answer": "Tug of War",
            "answer_options": [
                "Hockey",
                "Dodgers ",
                "Football",
                "Tug of War"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "medium",
            "question": "Which country won the 2015 Rugby World Cup?",
            "correct_answer": "New Zealand",
            "answer_options": [
                "Australia ",
                "England",
                "Wales",
                "New Zealand"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "general knowledge",
            "difficultly": "easy",
            "question": "Who was the first British monarch to visit New Zealand?",
            "correct_answer": "Elizabeth II",
            "answer_options": [
                "Victoria",
                "Edward VIII",
                "George VI",
                "Elizabeth II"
            ]
        }
    ]
}
